hey guys jti here I'm going to give you
the download on how to use chopsticks
and how to look good doing it come on
over first Chopstick is a writing grip
right with your thumb index in Middle um
it's almost like a paintbrush grip or a
writing grip second Chopstick goes into
uh the Gap here and is supported by the
ring finger and what you want to do is
articulate that that that that pencil or
that writing grip um Chopstick down to
the other one the other one actually is
fixed and never moves you only move the
top Chopstick and you've done your job
you should be able to grab a piece of
food and pull it up just like that and
it'd be really awesome you start
catching flies like this from the oh
there you go